[Music]
all right this is a login video just
showing you what you need to do to get
yourself online with thinker so the
first thing you need to go do is you
need to go to tinker comm tinker is
spelt with a y so T Y in keer comm
assuming that you've got to login for me
you can actually just click on sign in
if you didn't get a login for me you'd
have to create an account but I made an
account for you there are three
different types of account on tinker
there's students which is what you are
there's teacher that's me and then if
you didn't get any help from anyone you
just signed in yourself you had to make
a parent account so I'm gonna show you
signing in just as a student because
this is what you should expect you can
see that I've done this once before so
it should be connecting with code 2020
and then your child's first and last
name all lowercase all smushed together
some people we had to add like a 2/4 or
something like that or if you didn't
provide the last name for this be first
name and then the password for everybody
is just CWC 20/20 so it's just the same
first characters are the same seven
first characters as in your username
right once you do that you just click on
enter on now you're into the tinkerer
system inside the tinkerer system you're
probably only in one class so you should
be in the in the connecting with code
camp there's a number of different
follow along activities and these things
are great for you to do anytime you want
it doesn't have to be with me as a
following video you can actually just
click on them and learn about them so
that's where I'll cut off this login
video but hopefully you can log in every
day see in the videos
[Music]